{
    "tileTypes": [
        {
            "uid": 103,
            "name": "sink-right-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "0",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "sink-right",
            "back": "sink-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 129,
                "g": 61,
                "b": 156
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 137,
            "name": "sink-right-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "1",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "sink-right",
            "back": "sink-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 129,
                "g": 61,
                "b": 156
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 187,
            "name": "wire-horizontal-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "0",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "wire-horizontal",
            "back": "wire-horizontal",
            "color": {
                "r": 192,
                "g": 28,
                "b": 40
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 237,
            "name": "wire-horizontal-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "1",
            "right": "1",
            "front": "wire-horizontal",
            "back": "wire-horizontal",
            "color": {
                "r": 4,
                "g": 158,
                "b": 244
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 260,
            "name": "clock-right-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "1",
            "back": "0",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 262,
            "name": "clock-right-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "1",
            "front": "0",
            "back": "1",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 264,
            "name": "clock-standalone-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "1",
            "back": "0",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 285,
            "name": "clock-standalone-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "anything",
            "right": "anything",
            "front": "0",
            "back": "1",
            "color": {
                "r": 100,
                "g": 100,
                "b": 100
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 317,
            "name": "NOT-right-0",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "0",
            "right": "1",
            "front": "NOT-right",
            "back": "NOT-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 38,
                "g": 162,
                "b": 105
            }
        },
        {
            "uid": 351,
            "name": "NOT-right-1",
            "up": "anything",
            "down": "anything",
            "left": "1",
            "right": "0",
            "front": "NOT-right",
            "back": "NOT-right",
            "color": {
                "r": 38,
                "g": 162,
                "b": 105
            }
        }
    ],
    "savedSubPlaneTilings": [],
    "mainPlaneTiling": {
        "tiles": [],
        "name": ""
    },
    "cachedPlaneTiling": {
        "tiles": [],
        "name": ""
    },
    "colorMap": {
        "0": {
            "r": 192,
            "g": 28,
            "b": 40
        },
        "1": {
            "r": 4,
            "g": 158,
            "b": 244
        },
        "ANYTHING": {
            "r": 0,
            "g": 0,
            "b": 0
        },
        "sink-right": {
            "r": 129,
            "g": 61,
            "b": 156
        },
        "wire-horizontal": {
            "r": 61,
            "g": 56,
            "b": 70
        },
        "NOT-right": {
            "r": 143,
            "g": 240,
            "b": 164
        }
    }
}